Guide to the Edward Davison Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1919-1960; Series IX; 0.42; (1 box)
  - Orage, A. R., 1932-1934 (Box 20)
  - Program for a Democratic Germany, 1944 (Box 20)
  - Ratcliffe, S. K., 1944-1945 (Box 20)
  - Rivers, William Halse, 1922 June 7 (Box 20)
  - Sandburg, Carl, 1953 (Box 20)
  - Sutherland, Donald, 1954 (Box 20)
  - Squire, J. C., undated (Box 20)
  - Stenbuck, Jack, undated (Box 20)
  - University of Colorado, 1937-1940 (Box 20)
  - Washington & Jefferson College, 1949 (Box 20)
  - Wilton Park Training Centre, 1946 (Box 20)
- Oversize, 0.17; (2 boxes)
  - Office of the Provost Marshal General Prisoner of War Special Projects Division, organizational chart (Series II.), undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - U.S. Army school center, Fort Getty- Fort Wetherill, organizational chart (Series II.), undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Davison, Natalie Weiner (Series V.), undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Evans, Anne (Series V.), undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Priestly, J. B. (Series V.), undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Group photographs (Series V.), 1943 November 4 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Unidentified (Series V.), undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Diplomas (Series VI.), 1921-1934; 2 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Certificates (Series VI.), 1896-1952 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - H., R. Untitled pen and ink drawing (Series VII.), undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Lindsay, Vachel. "Butterflies" (Series VII.), undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Robinson, Boardman. Untitled crayon drawing (Series VII), circa 1940 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - "How the Army teaches democracy to German prisoners of war" (poster) (Series VIII.), undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Clippings, Personal (Series VIII.), undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Clippings, Military (Series VIII.), 1942-1946; 3 (Box 21 (Oversize))
  - Clippings, General (Series VIII.), 1922-1947; 4 (Box 22 (Oversize))